现在你已经添加了URI进WeatherContract
Now that you've added the URI
information to the WeatherContract, step
这是构建ContentProvider的第二步。我要解释一下。
two of building our Content Provider,
I've got some explaining to do.
在WeatherContract一开始的地方，
At the beginning of our WeatherContract,
你能看到我们定义了CONTENT_AUTHORITY
you can see we defined
the CONTENT_AUTHORITY.
下面我们添加了URI基本路径的字符串
Next we added strings for
the BASE paths for our URIs.
注意这些路径是怎样和我们的两个数据表关联的
Note how these paths
match our two tables.
对于每一个数据表里的LocationEntry和WeatherEntry
For each of our tables,
LocationEntry and WeatherEntry,
我们创建了一个CONTENT_URI。它表达了每一个数据表的基础地址
we created a CONTENT_URI that represents
the base location for each table.
另外Contract里面为了方便有一些辅助函数
Something else that is convenient to
have in the contract are functions to
它们帮助建造ContentProvider的查询语句
help build the Content Provider queries.
现在，对于一些用于URI建造和解码方程
Now, for some URI builders and
decoder functions for WeatherEntry.
有它们是很方便的，因为它们让你的代码
It's convenient to have these, as it
makes fewer places in your code aware of
不需要知道URI真正的构建法则，只在Contract里保留这些繁琐的内容
the actual URI in coding,
keeping this knowledge in the contract.
像设置地址这样的字符串可以用appendPath
Strings such as the location setting
can be appended with the appendPath
这个方程来扩展
function.
很快你将要实现这个buildWeatherLocation方程
You'll be implementing the build
weather location function shortly.
这种情况，添加额外的路径到这个URI
In this case adding an additional
path to the URI does not
不会改变它的类型
change the type of the URI.
看，它们都是DIR类型
See, they're both type DIR.
我们也能使用这些方程来添加潜在有用的查询参数
We can also use these functions to add
potentially useful query parameters.
这种情况，我们使用一个查询参数startDate
In this case, we use a query
parameter for the start date.
查询参数是很有用的，当我们有一个固定的数据库查询句
Query parameters are useful when, for
when we have a fixed database query that
基于这个查询句我们想要有一些额外的限制
we want to have some limited
parametrization for.
这种情况，它会是我们把两个数据表JOIN在一起的一个参数
In this case it will be a parameter for
our join between the two tables.
除此之外
More on that later.
URI看起来就像网页的URL，
URI queries look just like
the queries you see in web URLs, and
并且允许我们添加更丰富更复杂的内容在URI Contract里面
give us the ability to add more richness
and complexity to our URI contract.
最终，我们有了这个方程，它创建URI包括了天气
Finally, we have this function that
builds a two part URI with both weather
和日期两个部分
and date segments.
下面我们有辅助函数把URI结构从我们的代码里隐藏了起来
Below this we have helper functions that
hide the URI structure from our code.
它从URI里提取信息并且把所有的相关知识集中在了一个地方
For retrieving values in the URI and
place all this knowledge in one place.
看看我们的这一串URIs，你能看到
Looking back at our list of URIs,
you can see that for
每一个我调用的URI返回一串的项目
each URI I called out whether
the URI returned a list of items.
被标识为DIR（文件夹）或者ITEM（单个文件）
By labeling it with dir for directory or
a single item by labeling it with item.
从ContentProvider返回的Cursor有唯一类型基于
Cursors returned from a content provider
have unique types based upon their
它们内容或是基础路径
content and
the base path used for the query.
Android使用类似于Internet媒体类型或是
Android uses a form similar
to the internet media type or
MIME类型来描述URI返回的类型
mime type to describe
the type returned by the URI.
能返回多个项目的Cursor有
Cursors that can return more
than one item are prefixed
CURSOR_DIR_BASE_TYPE字符串作为前缀
by the CURSOR_DIR_BASE_TYPE string.
当Curosr只返回一个项目时，使用
While cursors that return only
a single item are prefixed by
CURSOR_ITEM_BASE_TYPE字符串作为前缀
the CURSOR_ITEM_BASE_TYPE string.
这里我们定义了地址和天气的类型
We define these types here for both
the location and the weather queries.